Guide to the Abe Burrows papers, 1904-1993
The New York Public Library. Billy Rose Theatre Division.
- Series II: General Correspondence, 1939-1982; 588315; 15 boxes
  - Sub-series 2 - Telegrams, 1947-1981; 588661; 3 boxes
    - Make a Wish opening night telegrams,., 1951 Apr 12-18; 588664; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Telegrams mostly to Abe Burrows on the opening at the Winter Garden.
      Martin, Hugh, 1914-
    - Two on the Aisle opening night telegrams,., 1951 June 11-July 14; 588665; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway openings in New Haven and San Francisco.
      Styne, Jule, 1905-
    - Two on the Aisle opening night telegrams,., 1951 July 19; 588666; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening at the Mark Hellinger Theatre.
    - Three Wishes for Jamie opening night telegrams,., 1952 Feb 1-4; 588667; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway opening, 1952 Feb 4, at the Shubert Theatre in New Haven, Connecticut.
      Blane, Ralph, 1914-
    - Three Wishes for Jamie opening night telegrams,., 1952 Mar 19-24; 588668; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening, 1952 Mar 21, at the Mark Hellinger Theatre. Two replies, 1952 Mar 31, attached.
    - Can-Can opening night telegrams,., 1953 Mar 21-24; 588669; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway opening, 1953 Mar 23, at the Shubert Theatre in Philadelphia.
      Porter, Cole, 1891-1964
    - Can-Can opening night telegrams,., 1953 May 6-8; 588670; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening, 1953 May 7, at the Shubert Theatre in New York City.
    - Guys and Dolls opening night telegrams,., 1953 May 28; 588671; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the opening at the Coliseum Theatre in London.
    - Reclining Figure opening night telegrams,., 1954 Sept 15-21; 588672; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway openings in New Haven and Philadelphia.
      Kurnitz, Harry
    - Reclining Figure opening night telegrams,., 1954 Oct 6-7; 588673; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening, 1954 Oct 7, at the Lyceum Theatre.
    - Silk Stockings opening night telegrams,., 1955 Feb 23-Mar 7; 588674; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 11)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening, 1955 Feb 24, at the Imperial Theatre.
    - Happy Hunting opening night telegrams,., 1956 Oct 20-25; 588675; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway opening at the Shubert Theatre in Philadelphia.
      Karr, Harold, 1921-1968
    - Happy Hunting opening night telegrams,., December 5, 1956 Dec 5-7; 588676; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening, 1956 Dec 6, at the Majestic Theatre in New York.
    - Say, Darling opening night telegrams,., 1958 Feb 19-Mar 4; 588677; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway openings at the Shubert Theatres in New Haven and Philadelphia.
      Bissell, Richard Pike
    - Say, Darling opening night telegrams,., 1958 Apr 2-4; 588678; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening, 1958 Apr 3, at the ANTA Theatre in New York City.
    - First Impressions opening night telegrams,., 1959 Jan 29-Mar 14; 588679; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway openings at the Shubert Theatre in New Haven and the Forrest Theatre in Philadelphia.
      Goldman, Robert
    - First Impressions opening night telegrams,., 1959 Mar 18-21; 588680; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening at the Alvin Theatre in New York City.
    - Golden Fleecing opening night telegrams,., 1959 Sept 9; 588681; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway opening at the Shubert Theatre in New Haven.
      Semple, Lorenzo, Jr; The golden fleecing
    - Golden Fleecing opening night telegrams,., 1959 Oct 14-15; 588682; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening, 1959 Oct 15, at the Henry Miller Theatre in New York City.
    - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying opening night telegrams,., 1961 Sept 1-5; 588683; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway opening, 1961 Sept 4, at the Shubert Theatre in Philadelphia.
    - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying opening night telegrams,., 1961 Oct 13-27; 588684; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening at the 46th Street Theatre in New York City.
    - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying opening night telegrams,., 1963 Mar 14-29; 588685; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the British openings at the Opera House in Manchester and the Shaftesbury Theatre in London.
    - What Makes Sammy Run? opening night telegrams,., 1964 Feb 26-28; 588686; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 10)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening at the 54th Street Theatre in New York City.
      Drake, Ervin
    - Cactus Flower opening night telegrams,., 1965 Sept 20-Nov 22; 588687; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 11)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the pre-Broadway openings at the National Theatre in Washington DC, 1965 Nov 4, and the Forrest Theatre in Philadelphia.
      Burrows, Abe, 1910-
    - Cactus Flower opening night telegrams,., 1965 Dec 8; 588688; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 12)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening at the Royale Theatre in New York City.
    - Holly Golightly opening night telegrams,., 1966 Oct 10-15; 588689; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 13)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the opening at the Forrest Theatre in Philadelphia.
    - Cactus Flower opening night telegrams,., 1967 Mar 4-6; 588690; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 14)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the London opening at the Lyric Theatre.
    - Forty carats opening night telegrams,., 1968 Dec 26; 588691; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 15)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening at the Morosco Theatre in New York City.
      Allen, Jay Presson, 1922-
    - Four on a Garden opening night telegrams,., 1971 Jan 29-31; 588692; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 16)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening at the Broadhurst Theatre in New York City.
    - No Hard Feelings opening night telegrams,., 1973 Mar 30-Apr 8; 588693; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 17)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening at the Martin Beck Theatre in New York City.
      Bobrick, Sam
    - Guys and Dolls opening night telegrams,., 1976 July 20-Aug 6; 588694; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 18)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening of a revival of Guys and Dolls at the Broadway Theatre in New York City.
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1947; 588695; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 19)
      Telegrams received by Burrows regarding his radio broadcasts.
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1948; 588696; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 20)
      Opening night telegrams received by Burrows for his nightclub shows at Ciro's on Sunset Strip in Hollywood, the Mayfair Room at the Blackstone Hotel in Chicago, Le Directoire in New York City, and other venues.
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1948-1981; 588697; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 21)
      Miscellaneous (non-opening night) telegrams received by Burrows.
    - Guys and Dolls opening night telegrams,., 1952 Jan 19 & Apr 20; 588698; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Two telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast at New York's 46th Street Theatre and later, at City Center.
    - Can-Can opening night telegrams,., 1953 Mar 23-May 7; 588699; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the Shubert Theatre in Philadelphia and New York.
    - Solid Gold Cadillac opening night telegrams,., 1953 Nov 5; 588700; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 3)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the Belasco Theatre in New York City.
      Teichmann, Howard; The solid gold cadillac
    - Silk Stockings opening night telegrams,., 1954 Nov 26; 588701; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the Shubert Theatre in Philadelphia.
    - Happy Hunting opening night telegrams,., 1956 Dec 6; 588702; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the Majestic Theatre in New York City.
    - Say, Darling opening night telegrams,., 1958 Apr 3; 588703; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast at the ANTA Theatre in New York City.
    - First Impressions opening night telegrams,., 1959 Mar 19; 588704; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the Alvin Theatre in New York City.
    - Golden Fleecing opening night telegrams,., 1959 Oct 15; 588705 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the Henry Miller Theatre in New York City.
    - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying opening night telegrams,., 1961 Oct 14; 588706; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 9)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the 46th Street Theatre in New York City.
    - What Makes Sammy Run? opening night telegrams,., 1964 Feb 26; 588707; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 10)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the 54th Street Theatre in New York City.
    - Cactus Flower opening night telegrams,., 1965 Dec 8; 588708; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 11)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the Royale Theatre in New York City.
    - Forty carats opening night telegrams,., 1968 Dec 26; 588709; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 12)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the Morosco Theatre in New York City.
    - Four on a Garden opening night telegrams,., 1971 Jan 29; 588710; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 13)
      Telegrams sent by Abe Burrows to members of the cast opening at the Broadhurst Theatre in New York City.
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1952; 588711; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 14)
      Miscellaneous opening night telegrams sent by Burrows.
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1953; 588712; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1954; 588713; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1955; 588714; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1956; 588715; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1957; 588716; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1958; 588717; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1959; 588718; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1960; 588719; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1961; 588720; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1962; 588721; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1963; 588722; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1964-1965; 588723; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1966-1967; 588724; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1968-1969; 588725; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows, 1960s?; 588726; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Telegrams / Abe Burrows,., 1950-1968; 588727; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 30)
      Miscellaneous non-opening night telegrams sent by Burrows.
- Series III: Production Files, 1912-1992; 588728; 54 boxes
  The productions series documents the productions with which Burrows was involved, followed by productions he worked on that were never produced, then scripts sent to him for consideration, and lastly show business work not specific to a certain production such as contracts and correspondence for radio and television appearances and with recording companies, correspondence with agents, material on copyright, and papers on the producing/investing organization he ran with his wife: Beresford Productions.
  - Sub-series 1 - By Title, 1950-1981; 588729; 45 boxes
    This sub-series consists of productions for which Abe Burrows was a writer, director, or both or in one case (Make a Wish), play doctor and in another case (First Gentleman), an investor. Within each production the arrangement is: scripts, partial scripts, drafts and revisions, designs, notes, sheet music, contact sheets, contracts, correspondence, financial papers, programs, clippings and photographs.
    Arranged chronologically by production.
    - Guys and Dolls by Frank Loesser, book by Jo Swerling and Abe Burrows, 588730
      - Script with handwritten revisions, 1950 Sept 11; 588731 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Script with handwritten revisions, 1950 Sept 11; 588732 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Production script, clean, n.d.; 588733 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        Includes light cues and property and costume plots.
      - "Working script," photocopy, n.d.; 588734 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Libretto, published, with a few pencilled notes, 1951; 588735 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Draft pages, partial script, n.d.; 588736 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Contact sheets, Broadway revival, 1976; 588737 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Contracts, 1951-1954; 588738 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Contracts, 1975-1976; 588739 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Contracts, 1985-1989; 588740 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Contracts, 1990-1991; 588741 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1950-1952; 588742 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1953-1959; 588743 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence on European productions, 1953-1959; 588744 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1969; 588745 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1976-1977; 588746 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1989; 588747 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, London production, 1981-1982; 588748 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Broadway revival, 1986-1989; 588749 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1991; 588750 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 588751 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence requesting tickets, 1950 Jan-1951 Jan; 588752 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence requesting tickets, 1951 Feb-1951 May; 588753 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Stock royalties, 1954-1959; 588754 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Stock royalties, 1960-1965; 588755 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Stock royalties, 1966-1968; 588756 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Stock royalties, 1969-1971; 588757 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Stock royalties, 1972-1979; 588758 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Stock royalties, 1980-1981; 588759 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Royalties from cast album (Decca), 1955-1961; 588760 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Royalties from cast album (Decca), 1962-1969, 1980; 588761 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence on motion picture deal, 1954-1955; 588762 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Receipts from motion picture, 1954-1960; 588763 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Receipts from motion picture, 1961-1974; 588764 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence on motion picture remake, 1976-1982; 588765 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Programs, 1950-1992; 588766 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Souvenir program and souvenir book, 1955 and 1982; 588767 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Clippings, 1950-1962; 588768 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Clippings, Broadway revival, 1976; 588769 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Clippings, London production, 1982; 588770 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Publicity materials, 1992; 588771 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Clippings, 1992; 588772 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Photographs, 1950-1992; 588773 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Make a Wish by Hugh Martin, book by Preston Sturges, 588774
      - Contract, 1951 Mar 20; 588775 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Program, 1951 Apr 18; 588776 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Clippings, 1951 Apr; 588777 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Two on the Aisle by Jules Styne, lyrics and sketches by Betty Comden and Adolph Green, 588778
      - Draft pages of script, n.d.; 588779 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Contracts, 1951-1952; 588780 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Receipts for pay, 1951 May 19-July 14; 588781 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Programs, 1951; 588782 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Clippings, 1951-1952; 588783 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Three Wishes for Jamie by Ralph Blane, book by Charles O'Neal and Abe Burrows, 588784
      - Script with song lyrics, n.d.; 588785 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Production script, n.d.; 588786 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        Includes cast list, cues, scenic breakdown, property list, hanging plots and inventory of sound and costumes.
      - Handwritten pages of script (draft revisions by Burrows), 588787 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Contracts, 1951; 588788 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Contracts, 1951-1953, 1980; 588789 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Letters to Burrows from Charles O'Neal, 1951; 588790 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1952-1953; 588791 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Stock royalties, 1956-1964; 588792 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Programs, 1952; 588793 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Clippings, 1952-1953; 588794 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Photographs, n.d.; 588795 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Can-Can by Cole Porter, book by Abe Burrows, 588796
      - Script, photocopied, 1965 Jan. 8; 588797 (Box 23, Folder 12)
        Includes blocking notes and cues and cast list.
      - Clean script, 1980 July 29; 588798 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Script with handwritten revisions, 1980-1981; 588799 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        Includes cast list, contact sheet and rehearsal and production schedule
      - Draft of Act I, 1953 Feb 17; 588800 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Draft of Act I, n.d.; 588801 (Box 24, Folder 3)
        Includes cast list of principals. Missing pages 2-11.
      - Clean script, n.d.; 588802 (Box 24, Folder 4)
        Adapted by Julian More for British production.
      - Clean script, 1988; 588803 (Box 24, Folder 5)
        [Revised script] adapted by Julian More for the London production.
      - Notes on Julian More adaptation, n.d.; 588804 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Clean script in Swedish, n.d.; 588805 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Scenes: drafts and revisions, 588806 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Scenes: handwritten drafts for Act I, 588807 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Scenes: handwritten drafts for Act II, 588808 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Scenes: handwritten drafts, unidentified, 588809 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous notes, 1952; 588810 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Research notes on Jane Avril, n.d.; 588811 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Research notes on Senator Berenger, n.d.; 588812 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Research notes on censorship, 1881-1882; 588813 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Research: issue of Crapouillot, n.d.; 588814 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Research: extracts from Daily Life in France from 1870 to 1900, n.d.; 588815 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Research: souvenir album from Folies Bergere, n.d.; 588816 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Photo of front page of Le Gaulois, 1888 Apr 6; 588817 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Research notes on the jury system, n.d.; 588818 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Research notes on pornography, 1905 and n.d; 588819 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Research: souvenir album from Tabarin (nightclub), n.d.; 588820 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Research notes on Toulouse-Lautrec, n.d.; 588821 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Research materials, visual, 1952 July and n.d; 588822 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Research notes: lists of names, n.d.; 588823 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous and sundry research notes, 588824 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Research clippings, 1912-1952; 588825 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Notes for actors, n.d.; 588826 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Notes on set and costumes, 588827 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Set designs: six thumbnail sketches by Jo Mielziner, n.d.; 588828 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - List of scene numbers, 1952 Nov 14; 588829 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Outline for Act I, n.d.; 588830 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Timing for musical numbers, 1952 Dec 29; 588831 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Lyrics by Cole Porter, 1952-1953; 588832 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Sheet music by Cole Porter, 1952-1953; 588833 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Contact sheets, 1953; 588834 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Contact sheet and schedule for Broadway revival, 1980 June; 588835 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Contracts, 1952-1954; 588836 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Contracts, 1965-1968; 588837 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Contracts, 1980; 588838 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Contracts, Argentinian production, 1963 July 29; 588839 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Contracts, Broadway revival, 1979-1980; 588840 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Contracts, English production, 1987-1988; 588841 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence with Louis H. Aborn, 1959-1982; 588842 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence with Abe Lastfogel, 1954; 588843 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Burrows' correspondence with Ernest Martin and Cy Feuer, 1952-1953; 588844 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence with Jo Mielziner, 1952 and n.d; 588845 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, A-Z, 1952-1981; 588846 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence on casting, 1952-1953; 588847 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Australian production, 1954-1955; 588848 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, British production, 1954 Oct; 588849 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Scandinavian productions, 1955-1984; 588850 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Broadway revival, 1979-1980; 588851 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, London revival, 1987-1988; 588852 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Remittance slips, 1955-1958; 588853 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Stock royalties, 1955-1959; 588854 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Stock royalties, 1960-1969; 588855 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Stock royalties, 1971-1979; 588856 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Stock royalties, Australian productions, 1955-1958; 588857 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Stock royalties, British productions, 1955-1956; 588858 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Stock royalties, Scandinavian productions, 1955-1956; 588859 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Stock royalties, Scandinavian productions, 1957-1959; 588860 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Publicity: Burrows notes on Martin Dibner's sketches, with published piece, 1953 Sept-Nov; 588861 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Publicity: Burrows, Director's work is never done (One year of Can-Can), 1954 April-May; 588862 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Publicity: drafts of an article by Karl Bernstein, n.d.; 588863 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Publicity: biographies for London production, ca. 1988; 588864 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Programs, 1953-1981; 588865 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Souvenir program, 1953; 588866 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Opening program for Alhambra Theatre, Bradford, England, 1986 Oct 30; 588867 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Souvenir program, Strand Theatre, London, 1988; 588868 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Clippings, 1953 and n.d; 588869 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Publicity: program, clippings and photographs from Scandinavian productions, 1955-1959; 588870 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Clippings, Broadway revival, 1979 and n.d; 588871 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Clippings, London production, 1988; 588872 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Photographs, n.d.; 588873 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Motion picture contracts, 1955; 588874 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence on motion picture financial matters, 1957-1958; 588875 (Box 27, Folder 17)